# Ahmed Ali Gawish

# **Front-End Developer**

**▲** AhmedGawish22@gmail.com

**\** 01064880594

**≡** 5 Sep 2001 **♀** Kafr Elsheikh - Egypt

https://github.com/ahmedgawish10

in https://linkedin.com/Ahmed-Gawish

# **Summary**

I am a Passionate Front-end developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs, NextJs and Angular. Gained Skills in creating responsive web designs as a trainee in (ITI), gained ability to collaborate effectively within a team. Committed to continually updating skills. Familiar with backend technologies such as PHP, MySOL

# **Education**

Bachelor of Technology and Information Systems, PortSaid University Cumulative Grade(GPA): Very Good with Honors

2019 - 2023

### **Work Experience**

Front-End Developer at Rukn

May, 2024 - Present

Front-End Developer on Upwork (Freelancer)

August, 2021 - Present

Convert Figma designs into responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, Tailwind, JavaScript, ReactJs

• Fullstack Web Developer at ITI

January, 2024 - May, 2024

develop web pages and build responsive websites using HTML3, CSS3, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, PHP, MySQL, Laravel, WordPress

Others: Docker, Git, Linux, CLI

Fundamentals Web Development Summer Training at ITI July, 2022 - August ,2022 Create and design responsive websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap

### **Technical Skills**

🖊 Front-End

• HTML5 Tailwind CSS ReactIS

TypeScript

CSS3

Material UI

Redux

Formik & Yup

SASS

• JavaScript

NextIS

React-hook-form & Zod

BootStrap5

• jQuery

Angular

Git & GitHub

# Back-End

• PHP

• My SQL

Strapi (CMS)

Laravel

Firebase

NodeJS

### **Projects**

### Graduation Project: Arduino Measure Diabetes

- Grade: Excellent
- **Description**: A sensor device inserted into the patient's arm for 14 days, which converts a signal to be received via Bluetooth to a mobile app for blood sugar monitoring.
  - Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap5, JavaScript, Reactjs
    - Arduino Product Website: Demo

#### Projects

### • Next & Strapi

Al-Jewar Travel Agency App: Demo

Technologies: HTML - CSS- Tailwind - JavaScript - Next.js - i18Next

Courses Tech App: Code

A learning platform designed for seamless educational experiences, built with **Next.js** and **Strapi** for content management, authentication by **Clerk**, payment integration with **Stripe**.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - Tailwind - JavaScript - Next.js - Strapi - Clerk - Stripe - Cloudnairy

#### PHP & MY SQL

Job Portal App: Code

Job portal application designed to simplify the hiring process for organizations. This web-based solution facilitates job postings and candidate applications.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - PHP - MY SQL

#### React & Firebase

Portfolio: Demo

Dashboard-ABrand: Demo

Dashboard for managing an e-commerce website, allowing admins to add and manage products. **Technologies**: HTML - CSS - JavaScript - Material UI - React - Firebase Realtime Database.

■ E-commerce-ABrand: Demo

E-commerce website designed to sell a variety of electronics, books, and clothing, **Technologies**: HTML - CSS - TypeScript - Material UI - React - Redux Toolkit - Firebase.

■ E-commerce: Demo

E-commerce website for the medical industry, facilitating the sale of a variety of medical healthy products. The application ensures a smooth shopping experience for customers.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - JavaScript - React - Redux Toolkit - react slick carousel - REST API

#### Angular

■ E-commerce: Demo

e-commerce website using Angular with user authentication and lazy Loading for optimized performance. The application uses local storage, ensuring a seamless shopping experience.

Technologies: HTML - CSS -Bootstrap -JavaScript - Angular - REST API

#### IavaScript

■ E-commerce Website: demo

# Personal Skills

- Good organizational, interpersonal and Communication skills.
- Strong attention to detail and ability to multitask effectively.
- problem solving and High flexibility in thinking.
- Time management skills.
- Self-study.

#### Languages

• Arabic mother tongue

**English** conversational